YU HAMADA

Web developer

- yuham1014@gmail.com
- (236) 308-3679
- 665 East 28th Avenue.
 Vancouver, BC, V5V 2N4.

EDUCATION

 Cornerstone International Community College of Canada Vancouver, Canada

Web & Mobile App Development with CO-OP

Sep, 2023 - Present

 Tokyo University of Science Tokyo, Japan

Bachelor of physics Apr, 2019 - Mar, 2023

SKILL

- Programming (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, Ruby on Rails, Python)
- Microsoft Office (Powerpoint, word, excel)
- Communication Skills
- Management Skills
- Critical Thinking
- Marketing Skills
- Teaching, Coaching Skills

LANGUAGE

- English
- Japanese

PROFILE

I'm a web developer with a passion for both coding and coaching.

With a solid background in developing software by online and teaching programming languages, I thrive in guiding others toward success.

And also with 4 years of coaching experience, I've developed effective communication skills and an ability to simplify complex concepts.

My passion for problem-solving and continuous learning keeps me engaged with the latest trends in the field.

I'm excited to bring my coding skills, coaching experience, and enthusiasm for learning to collaborative projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Coaching of Programming and Developing an software tool | Side Business by online

2022 - present

- communicate with students and manage their studing schedule
- coaching programming and developing an software
- solve the problems of students
- market research in my field of expertise

Teacher, Tutor | Toshin High School 2019 - 2020

- developed optimal study roadmaps to guide student learning effectively.
- communicated efficiently with students, managing their study schedules to maximize their academic progress.
- provided instruction in Mathematics, physics, and Chemistry.

Teacher, Management of students | School IE 2020 – 2023

- developed optimal study roadmaps to guide student learning effectively.
- communicated efficiently with students, managing their study schedules to maximize their academic progress.
- provided instruction in Mathematics, physics, and Chemistry.

Server, hospitality staff | Kamadoka (Japanese Sake Restaurant) 2020 – 2021

- provided meals tailored to each customer's specific requirements.
- communicated effectively with customers, introducing recommendations to enhance their dining experience.
- delivered the highest level of hospitality to ensure customer satisfaction.

As a hospitality specialist, I effectively resolved conflicts between customers.

Hospitality Specialist | McDonald's in Japan 2021 – 2022

- maintained a high standard of cleanliness and meticulously prepared rooms to provide a welcoming environment for guests.
- managed and trained staff, successfully promoting them within an eight-month period